(Sheldon:)- Do you know what that is?
- Of course not.
(Sheldon:)Homeostasis refers to a system's ability
to regulate its internal environment.
Yeah, and maintain a constant condition
of properties like temperature or pH.
(Penny:)Worst bedtime story ever.
(Sheldon:)My point is,
I don't like when things change.
(Sheldon:)So, regardless of your feelings, I would
like you to continue dating Leonard.
(Sheldon:)And also, while we're on the subject,
you recently changed your shampoo.
(Sheldon:)I'm not comfortable
with the new scent.
Will you please stop this madness
and go back to green apple?
(Penny:)Okay, honey, I have a lot to figure out.
(Penny:)And until I do,
you are not to say a word to Leonard.
(Penny:)- Do you understand?
- I do.
(Sheldon:)- You clear on the shampoo issue?
- Get out.